<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>4xFlavor</title>
 <link href="http://www.seamustuohy.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.seamustuohy.com/"/>
 <updated>2012-11-04T19:14:04-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://seamustuohy.com/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Seamus Tuohy</name>
   <email>s2e@seamustuohy.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>German for German's Sake</title>
   <link href="http://www.seamustuohy.com/all/writing/2010/11/10/German_for_Germans_Sake.html"/>
   <updated>2010-11-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.seamustuohy.com/all/writing/2010/11/10/German_for_Germans_Sake</id>
   <content type="html">  &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.deutschlandstiftung.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;German Foundation for Integration&lt;/a&gt; is releasing a series of ads aimed at encouraging immigrants to learn German and integrate culturally. This, just after the news that &amp;#8220;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-11559451&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the German Multi-Cultural Society has failed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#8220;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read a report on &lt;a href=&quot;http://saalt.org/attachments/1/From%20Macacas%20to%20Turban%20Toppers%20Report.small.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&amp;#8220;The Rise in Xenophobic and Racist Rhetoric in American Political Discourse&amp;#8221;&lt;/a&gt; From &lt;a href=&quot;http://saalt.presstools.org/node/36213?q=node%2F36213&quot;&gt;SAALT&lt;/a&gt; the other day that has put me on alert for Xenophobia and Nationalism. The news recently in Germany is looking quite grim for immigrants. No &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.guardian.co.uk/world/2010/sep/13/france-deportation-roma-illegal-memo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;worse&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-11323053&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;than&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.novinite.com/view_news.php?id=121805&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;France&lt;/a&gt;, but quite grim. I have no theory on the why &amp;#8211; &lt;a href=&quot;http://nohomonationalism.blogspot.com/2010/06/judith-butler-refuses-berlin-pride.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Butler&lt;/a&gt; is surely on this- but, Nationalistic and Xenophobic spasms are being seen in Germany, as they are surely seen all over the world, and it fucking terrifies me.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How Ridiculous Laws Get Made</title>
   <link href="http://www.seamustuohy.com/all/writing/2010/11/05/How-Ridiculous-Laws-Get-Made.html"/>
   <updated>2010-11-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.seamustuohy.com/all/writing/2010/11/05/How-Ridiculous-Laws-Get-Made</id>
   <content type="html">  &lt;p&gt;A western couple traveled to the Maldives to get their wedding vows renewed. Upon arriving they paid $1,300 to their hotel for a traditional ceremony that would &amp;#8220;mark a milestone in your amazing journey together&amp;#8221;. They were promised a religious ceremony, a official certification, and a planting of a coconut tree. At the &amp;#8220;wedding&amp;#8221; ceremony instead of reciting the stated traditional prayer and renewal of the vows the officiant instead in his native tongue insulted, and made lascivious comments about the couple. Even the marriage certificate that the officiant read from was merely and employment contract. This was a horrific breach of trust. But, that is not what worries me. What worries me is a series of quotes from government officials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Maldives&amp;#8217; Deputy Tourism Minister, Ismail Yasir,&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-south-asia-11644328&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; stated&lt;/a&gt; &amp;#8220;We have asked the resort to inform us what action they have taken. We  have also requested a formal inquiry into the matter from the police,&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The Maldive countries currently survive on tourist dollars. A scandal in the tourist sector could be devastating to the region. (I will point out that I started this posting the day the incident went live on BBC, with the idea that the Maldive Government would inact some silly law banning swear words in wedding ceremonies.) But, instead I discover today that the Government decided to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.smh.com.au/travel/travel-news/infamous-insult-video-leads-maldives-to-change-laws-20101105-17gcd.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; ban marriages performed in any language other than the spoken tongue of the marrying couple.&lt;/a&gt; Immediate aims and concerns overshadowing long term goals. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haveeru.com.mv/english/details/33243&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Very short term aims considering some of the response.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Implications of a Petroleum-less Military</title>
   <link href="http://www.seamustuohy.com/all/writing/2010/10/25/Implications_of_a_Petroleum-less-Military.html"/>
   <updated>2010-10-25T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.seamustuohy.com/all/writing/2010/10/25/Implications_of_a_Petroleum-less-Military</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;What are the implications of The American Military Infrastructure going green?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnas.org/files/documents/publications/CNAS_Working_Paper_EnergyMap_InitialFindings_Burke_Dec2008_1.pdf&quot;&gt;&amp;#8220;Center for a New American Security&amp;#8221; study&lt;/a&gt; aimed at exploring a post-petroleum military makes some great points as to the why, and the how, but only hints at some of the broader repercussions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;A successful transition away from petroleum will produce financial, operational and strategic gains. Reducing dependence on petroleum will help ensure the long-term ability of the military to carry out its assigned missions — and help ensure the security of the nation&amp;#8230;Finally, moving beyond petroleum will allow DOD to lead in the development of innovative technologies that can benefit the nation more broadly, while signaling to the world that the United States has as innovative and adaptable force.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;p&gt;With petroleum comprising 77% of the DOD&amp;#8217;s energy use ,and the DOD comprising aprox. 80% of the federal governments energy use, the DOD&amp;#8217;s plan to replace petroleum energy use in the military over the next 40 years is going to create a long term market for alternative energy suppliers and researchers. But, how will this open field be distributed among the current system of wealth? Can we take control, through innovation, to pull power away from the companies that have monopolies on energy and distribute it to the people?&lt;/p&gt;



</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>